Mario Llesta Muñoz

Madrid, Spain · linkedin.com/in/mariollesta · +34 642 77 59 34 · llesta.mario@gmail.com

About 3 years of experience working in IT companies in different roles. Passionate about software development, QA and DevOps methodology. I develop Open Source projects in my GitHub profile.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Madrid, Spain July 2024 – Present

Open Cloud Factory - Cipherbit

Software QA Automation

- Performing manual and automated test case and execution tasks on OpenNAC.
- Design and development of a Playwright style guide and best practices for the QA team..
- Design and development of integration, API and E2E tests with Playwright.
- Performing tasks to improve integration and continuous delivery pipelines using Jenkins.
- Use of GitLab and Git for version control of the test developments performed.
- QA reporting and task management using Redmine.

Madrid, Spain

September 2022 – July 2024

Open Cloud Factory

Professional Services Specialist

- Support for OpenNAC/EMMA project implementations, including Linux system administration and MySQL/MariaDB database management.
- Automated virtual environment deployments using Ansible playbooks and data analysis with Elasticsearch.
- Management of network access policies, creation of device profiles and technical documentationca.

Madrid, Spain

February 2022 - July 2022

NTT DATA Europe & LATAM

Solution Analyst Intern

- Developed Al-driven software solutions using Multiagent Systems, Java and Spring Boot; deployed and managed systems with Kafka, Kubernetes, PostgreSQL and MongoDB.

PROJECTS

Contribution to John Crickett's Coding Challenges Open Source project.

- CLI Wordcount and Load Balancer

EDUCATION

Leganes, Madrid, Spain September 2022

UNIVERSIDAD CARLOS III de MADRID

Bachelor's Degree in Telecommunication Technologies Engineering

Final Project: Design and development of a serious game in Unity 3D with a predictive model for student assessment. Grade: 9.4/10

SKILLS

- Python FastAPI, Reflex | Javascript, React, Tailwind CSS
- PostgreSQL | Linux, Bash scripting | Ansible, Jenkins | Playwright
- Spanish native. Fluent in English.